in this quick demo I'm going to show how
在这个快速演示中，我将展示如何
you can deploy a spring boot application
您可以部署Spring Boot应用程序
from your STS 4 workspace directly to
从您的STS 4工作区直接
plot foundry the first thing we're going
铸造厂是我们要做的第一件事
to do is select a boot dashboard and
要做的是选择启动仪表板，
create a cloud foundry target I'll have
创建我将拥有的Cloud Foundry目标
to put in my credentials here to log
在这里输入我的凭据进行登录
into cloud foundry and then we can
进入云代工厂，然后我们可以
choose to store our password or an auth
选择存储我们的密码或身份验证
token or not store it I like the auth
令牌或不存储它，我喜欢身份验证
token option because it's still secure
令牌选项，因为它仍然安全
but I don't have to type my password
但我不必输入密码
every time then we click select space
每次我们点击选择空间
and it's going to show us which spaces
并向我们​​展示哪些空间
are available to us I pick this one this
可供我们选择这个
is the one that I always use for demos
是我一直用于演示的那个
let's go ok once I've created my target
创建目标后就可以了
it appears here in the boot dashboard
它显示在启动仪表板中
and when you expand it you can see your
当您展开它时，您可以看到
applications and services there are no
应用程序和服务没有
applications right now but there are two
现在有两个应用程序
services available that I could use in
我可以在其中使用的可用服务
the applications I deploy there's a
我部署的应用程序有一个
Eureka and a rabbit and cube service
尤里卡和兔子和立方体服务
there that I could use okay so to deploy
在那里我可以使用，所以可以部署
my application the first thing I usually
我的申请通常是我的第一件事
do is create a manifest GMO file and
要做的就是创建清单GMO文件，
called foundry deployment manifest but
称为铸造厂部署清单，但
some of the details of how I want might
我想要的一些细节可能
have deployed I already did that ahead
已经部署了，我已经提前完成了
of time to speed things up a little bit
有时间加快速度
so here's the manifest I'm going to use
这是我要使用的清单
and then I just have to drag-and-drop
然后我只需要拖放
the application from the local services
来自本地服务的应用程序
from the local application section of
从的本地应用程序部分
the dashboard on to the remote section
仪表板到远程部分
when I drop it a dialog pops up and you
当我放下它时，会弹出一个对话框，您
see that it already selected my manifest
看到它已经选择了我的清单
because it found it in my project and I
因为它在我的项目中找到了
could then change it if I wanted to I
然后可以根据需要更改它
could do a manual deployment instead
可以手动部署
which will ignore the manifest and let
这将忽略清单并让
me type parameters manually or I can
我可以手动输入参数，也可以
just accept this manifest or I can make
只要接受这份清单，否则我可以
changes to the manifest if I wanted to
如果我想更改清单
I'm just gonna do everything the way it
我会做所有事情
is and click OK here and there you go
是，然后单击“确定”，然后转到那里
it's gonna go through and start
它会经历并开始
deploying man this is gonna take about a
部署人员这大约需要一个
minute maybe so while it's doing that
分钟可能是这样
we do a few show a little bit of a demo
我们做一些演示
of the editor feature so you can see
编辑器功能的视图，以便您可以看到
that when I hover over things here you
当我将鼠标悬停在这里时，
get the documentation for these various
获取有关这些各种文档
properties so that's convenient you go
属性，方便您前往
actually have to go online and find the
实际上必须上网查找
documentation also when you type it will
键入文件时也会
give you which properties are valid and
给你哪些属性是有效的
again you see documentation alongside it
再次，您会看到旁边的文档
so let's for example say I want to
举例来说，我想
change the host from its default to
将主机从默认设置更改为
super chat instead and maybe I want to
超级聊天，也许我想
add a service as well and notice that
还要添加服务并注意
when I add a service here that it knows
当我在这里添加服务时
about the services on this target and
关于此目标的服务以及
you get dynamic content assist based on
您将基于以下内容获得动态内容帮助
that so I can select you recap PWS as an
这样我就可以选择将PWS概括为
extra service here and in the meantime I
在此期间，我的额外服务
think my application should be about
认为我的申请应该是关于
Daum deploy okay so my application is
Daum可以部署，所以我的应用程序是
deployed once your application is
一旦您的应用程序被部署
deployed you can easily open it just
部署就可以轻松打开它
double-click it in the boot dashboard it
在启动仪表板中双击它
opens the corresponding web page in a
在页面中打开相应的网页
browser and see my chat application here
浏览器并在此处查看我的聊天应用程序
I'm not going to demo the application
我不会演示该应用程序
because that's really not the point of
因为那真的不是重点
the demo so the thing I want to demo
演示，所以我想演示的东西
next is what you can do once you make
接下来就是一旦你做
changes for example I made some changes
改变，例如我做了一些改变
to the deployment manifest maybe you
到部署清单，也许你
could make changes to your app itself as
可能会更改您的应用本身
well in both cases you might want to
在两种情况下都可能要
redeploy your application and apply
重新部署您的申请并申请
those changes to the Cloud Foundry
这些对Cloud Foundry的更改
deployment so that's easy to select your
部署，因此很容易选择您的
application and press restart button and
应用程序，然后按重启按钮，然后
what you will see is when the app
您将看到的是应用程序何时
restarts because I made changes to the
重新启动，因为我对
manifest we get this kind of a pop-up
清单，我们会得到这种弹出窗口
that warns us that some changes have
警告我们有些变化
been made and this is this but what this
已制成，这是这，但这是什么
shows is basically on this side here is
节目基本上在这边
the state of the application as it is
应用程序的状态
found currently on Cloud Foundry
当前在Cloud Foundry上找到
compared to what the manifests that we
相比我们所表现的
are using says and our manifest has
使用说，我们的清单有
changed a few things this diff dialog
改变了这个差异对话框的一些东西
shows it very clearly for example it
非常清楚地显示它，例如
shows that I've changed the host name
显示我已更改主机名
and I've added a service to my
我已经为我添加了服务
deployment now I can either use the
现在部署，我可以使用
manifest as is by clicking this button
单击此按钮即可显示
forget about the changes I just made and
忘记我刚才所做的更改，
just click forget manifest or make some
只需单击“忘记清单”或制作一些
changes in this dialog
此对话框中的更改
so for example let's say I changed my
例如，假设我更改了我的
mind about adding a service but I still
介意添加服务，但我仍然
want to change the host name I can just
要更改主机名，我可以
change this here and say use manifest
在此更改并说使用清单
and you can see that it removed the
您会看到它删除了
service from my manifest and now the
从我的清单到现在的服务
deployment is starting again now this is
现在再次开始部署
going to take a little while but this is
需要一点时间，但这是
more or less where I wanted to end my
或多或少我想结束我的地方
demo so I hope you enjoyed it and thanks
演示，所以我希望你喜欢它，谢谢
for watch
观看
you
您